right say welcome brothers and sisters
to another Wednesday question and answer
will we open up with the Ten
Commandments that God commanded the
whole world to keep brother James yes
sir and God spake all these words saying
I am the Lord thy God which have brought
thee out of the land of Egypt out of the
house of bondage Thou shalt have no
other gods before me Thou shalt not make
unto thee any Graven image or any
likeness of anything that is in heaven
above or that is in the earth beneath or
that is in the water under the Earth
Thou shalt not bow down thyself to them
nor serve them for I the Lord thy God am
a jealous God visiting the iniquity of
the fathers upon the children until the
third and four generation of them that
hate me and showing Mercy unto thousands
of them that love me and keep my
Commandments Thou shalt not take the
name of the Lord thy God in vain for the
Lord will not hold him Guiltless that
taketh his name in vain remember the
Sabbath day to keep it holy six days
shalt thou labor and do all thy work but
the seventh day is the Sabbath of the
Lord thy God in it Thou shalt not do any
work thou nor thy son nor thy daughter
thy man's servant nor thy maid servant
nor thy cattle nor thy stranger that is
within thy gates for in six days the
Lord made Heaven and Earth the sea and
all that in is and resteth the seventh
day wherefore the Lord blessed the
Sabbath day and hollowed it honor thy
father and thy mother that thy days may
be long upon the land which the Lord thy
God giveth thee Thou shalt not kill Thou
shalt not commit adultery Thou shalt not
steal Thou shalt not bear false witness
against thy neighbor Thou shalt not
covet thy neighbor's house Thou shalt
not covet thy neighbor's wife nor is
man's servant nor his maid servant nor
his Ox nor his ass nor anything that is
thy neighbors I read Exodus 20 verses
1-1 17 may the Lord add a blessing to
the reading of this word in Jesus name
we pray amen am
amen so here on question and answer you
can ask us a question and we'll answer
it according to the King James Bible and
if we cannot find the answer we will
seek further counsel to bring you an
answer at a later time the question we
will not answer are vague and long
scripture questions as well as questions
of debate we are not here to debate we
are here to spread the true Gospel of
Jesus so please be as direct as possible
with your questions so we can be as
direct as possible with our answers out
of the King James Bible no other Bibles
or books will be acknowledged on this
program also keep in mind this is a live
stream so feel free to send in your
questions that pertain to everlasting
life we just ask that you keep your
questions to a two scripture maximum let
me introduce to you the family that's on
the panel this evening we got brother
Jerome Grace and peace Brother Dre good
evening brother Julius good evening
everybody brother James good evening
everyone sister Deborah good evening
brother
Sean good evening and we have the guest
caller with us and I'm brother Cornell
sister Deborah what is our first
question of the
evening uh there
are uh there are held over questions
that will be answered first before
getting into tonight's Q&A uh brother
Santana says is this the correct way to
worship as Abraham in Genesis 17
verse3 Moses in Exodus
34:8 and Jesus in Matthew
26:39 by falling on your face or bowing
your head towards the Earth all right I
see they added three scriptures in there
one over our limit but we gonna be nice
brother Julius please share some light
well uh I went to all those scriptures
that the uh person that asked the
question uh and they all uh until then
are falling down to the Earth on their
face and worshiping so you can read
those scriptures on your own but uh
let's go to Revelation the 22nd
chapter okay you could do that if you
want to you could I have done that I
have fell on my face and fell on and and
and bowed down and that's individual
choice you could do that if you want to
but here's what the book say also
revelation 22 James read verses 8 and
N revelation 22 and8 says and I John saw
these things and heard them and when I
had heard and seen I fell down to
worship before the feet of the Angel
which showed me these things yeah like
the other three scriptures you fell down
and worship God now verse n Go ahead
then sayith he unto me see thou do it
not for I am thy fellow servant and of
thy Brethren the prophets and of them
which keep the sayings of this book
worship God so the answer is how do you
correctly worship God you could bow down
in prayer you could lift up holy hands
but the best way that you worship God
you keep the sayings of this book Jesus
said if you love me keep my Commandments
James the 1 chapter verse 22 he said
don't be just hearers of the words be
doers of the words that's how you
worship God that's all I got Cornel
all right yes sir and hey pray without
ceasing that's what the book say too
right brother you're praying yeah you
could do that that's what you're doing
that's right all right thank you for
that as we move on to our next question
moving on deor Deborah Davis asks will
there be sin in Jesus
Kingdom Julius is there going to be sin
when Jesus Come into his kingdom let's
let the book tell you expressly let's go
to Isaiah the 65th
chapter
okay Jesus going to rule and Reign his
kingdom for a thousand years but it will
still be Flesh and Blood here and that
will be ruled over by Spirit beings
Isaiah 65 give me verses 18 to 20
brother James Isaiah
658 to 20 when you get it my brother go
ahead and read it but be ye glad and
rejoice forever in that which I created
for behold I create Jerusalem a
rejoicing and her people a joy uhhuh and
I will rejoice in Jerusalem and joy in
my people and the voice of weeping shall
be no more heard in her nor the voice of
crying uhhuh there shall be no more then
an infant of days nor an old man that
hath not filled his days for the child
shall die a 100 years old but the sinner
be hundred years old shall be a cursed
but the what the sinner being 100 years
old why because he has not repented and
turn from his
sin that's the best I could do
Cornel all right yes sir also the wolf
and the lamb shall dwell together at
that time thank you for that brother
hope that answered that question as we
move on to our next next one miss Wade
asked in Jeremiah 31: 29
what is meant the Lord said he will sow
the house of Israel and the house of
Judah are they not the
same brother Jerome what you
say yeah they're the same people but
let's go read that verse that you gave
um Jeremiah
31 verse
29 okay in those days they shall say no
more the F the fathers have eaten a sour
grape and the children's teeth are set
on
edge okay um that verse right there is
not really dealing with the question
that you asked it's actually verse
27 so read that verse 27 for behold the
days come sayeth the Lord that I will
swow the house of Israel and the house
of Judah with the seed of man and with
the seed of Beast yeah so the Lord G
bring his people the children of
Israel he gonna bring the three tribes
that's under the Stick of Judah and he G
to also bring the nine tribes which is
Under The Stick of
Israel okay and all of them the Lord
goingon to bring them right back to
their own land he going to SW them in
that land and he going to sow beasts on
that land too he going to take care of
them he going to do them better than he
did their
forefathers okay so now let's go to the
uh eth verse stay in that chapter skip
up to verse eight we going to do some
skipping read verse eight behold I will
bring them from the North country and
gather them from the coast of the earth
and with them the Blind and the lame the
woman with child and her that travaileth
with child together a great company
shall return thither verse 11 and 12 for
the Lord hath redeemed Jacob and
ransomed him from the hand of him that
was stronger than he therefore they
shall come and sing in the height of
Zion and shall flow together to the
goodness of the Lord for wheat and for
wine and for oil and for the young of
the flock and of the herd and their soul
shall be as a water garden and they
shall not sorrow anymore at all verse
14 and I will satiate the soul of the
priest with fatness and my people shall
be satisfied with my goodness sayeth the
Lord and verse 23-
25 thus sayeth the Lord of hosts the god
of Israel as yet they shall use this
speech in the land of Judah and in the
cities thereof when I shall bring again
their captivity the Lord bless thee Oh
habitation of justice and mountain of
Holiness and there shall dwell in Judah
itself and in all the cities thereof
together the husband men and they that
go forth with flocks for I have satiated
the weary soul and I have replenished
every sorrowful Soul yeah he even going
to restore the flock like you just said
in 24 animals he gonna s animals in the
land too yeah and so yeah them the them
the um that's the whole house of Israel
that's what he talking about and they
that he going to make them one he going
to make them one nation again they split
in two right now but he going to bring
them back and make them one nation and
it tell you that in Ezekiel the 37th
chapter so just read 37th chapter and it
tell you about it verse 15 through
22 that's all I got
on all right thank you for that light
hope that answered the question as we
move on to our next moving on me too for
you Jan says in Hosea 1 verses 2 3 and 4
can you explain what took place
regarding these
verses okay any want to know what's
going on in Hosea 1 let's go there James
and pick it up at that verse two read it
to the four the GU caller will take it
from there okay Hosea 1 2-4 says the
beginning of the word of the Lord by
Hosea and the Lord said to Hosea go take
unto thee a wife of whoredoms and
children of whoredoms for the land hath
committed great whoredom parting from
the Lord so he went and took Goomer the
daughter of deam which conceived and
bear him a son and the Lord said unto
him call his name jazreel for yet a
little while and I will avenge the blood
of jazrael upon the house of juu and
will cause to Cease the kingdom of the
House of
Israel saying here he using uh uh Amos
here to go
and marry aoah because
Israel is the nation that the Lord
called a whole because we have committed
hom with
everybody so and he said because of that
he going to cause the Nations to cease
now let's go into Ezekiel 23rd chapter
read 1 through 5 and Skip down to verse
19 okay Ezekiel 20 23 1-5 says the word
of the Lord came again unto me saying
son of man there were two women the
daughters of one mother and they
committed whoredoms in Egypt they
committed whoredoms in their youth there
were their breast pressed and there they
bruised the T the teeths of their
virginity and the names of them were
aholah the Elder and ahabah her sister
and there were mine and they were mine
and they bear Sons and Daughters thus
were their names Samaria is aholah and
Jerusalem aabot and ahola played the
Harlot when she was mine and she doted
on her lovers as the syrians her
neighbors and then you said drop down to
what
verse 23 23
verse I said verse n okay verse nine
wherefore I have delivered her into the
hand of her lovers into the hand of the
Assyrians upon whom she
doed okay so Israel serve everybody's
God the Ser God and everybody else in
other words and when they serve all them
them Nations God they was committing
whoredom okay so now the one that last
one she committed wh was was with the
Assyrians and the Assyrians are the ones
that CA them to cease to be a nation
let's go into second Kings 17th chapter
verse I want you to read verse 16 and
17 okay that was Second
Kings what chapter again
sir uh Second Kings 17th chapter okay
vers 16 and 17 first okay versus 2 Kings
17: 16 and 17 says and they left all the
Commandments of the Lord their God and
made them molten images even two calves
and made a Grove and worshiped all the
host of heaven and served bael and they
caused their sons and their daughters to
pass through the fire and use divination
and enchantments and sold themselves to
do evil in the sight of the Lord to
provoke him to
anger and that's that horor dealing with
Paul false skip down to verse 22 read
verse 22 and 23 let's see what the Lord
did to him verse verse 22 says for the
children of Israel walked in all the
sins of jeroboam which he did they
departed not from them until the Lord
removed Israel out of his sight and as
he had said by all his servants the
prophets so was Israel carried away out
of their own land to Assyria unto this
day okay so that's what he said is
Israel was also called jezrael so
because of they H they dealing with
every nation's pagan gods and with bail
and then them two golden cast that jail
Bor made after the nation split the
committed whing with all them Pagan God
and so the last one they committed
whoredom with was the uh uh was the
Assyrians and those are the ones that
carried him out of the land and Israel
as a nation has ceased from that day to
this
one that's all this about the horish
people but use a horish woman show you
the
end that's all I gotta say all right
hope that answer today question as we
move on to our next next one MJ hello
ask for you to explain the difference
between statutes ordinance and
judgments all right brother Julius the
difference statutes are written
laws ordinances are how you the
procedure or how you carry out those
written laws and the judgments is the
reward of the penalty of the
law again you got your
statutes is your written laws your
ordinance on how you carry out the
written law and then the judgment is the
penalties or the rewards of keeping or
breaking that law let me give you a real
quick example Exodus chapter
12 Exodus chapter 12 and verse begin
reading that verse brother Jam verse
43 okay Exodus 12:43 says now you got
the Passover you got the Passover okay
now 43 go ahead and the Lord said unto
Moses and Aaron this is the ordinance of
the Passover there shall No Stranger eat
thereof uhhuh but every man's servant
that is bought for money when thou has
circumcised him then shall he eat
thereof so that's enough of that right
there but that's the way you carry out
that's the ordinance you're carrying out
the pth pass over but then the Lord tell
you if you read further no
uncircumstantial all right thank you for
that brother as we move on to our next
question next question Victor L asked
for you to explain how you can destroy
yourself in Ecclesiastes 7
verse6 oh yeah a lot of ways to do that
Dre what you say let's go and read that
ecclesiastics 7 and 16 and we gon to
skip and read one other verse go ahead
brother be not righteous over much
neither make thyself over wise why
should thou destroy
thyself that's right because when you
make yourself wise you can skip down to
verse uh
20 for there is not a just man upon
Earth that doeth good and sinth not they
all have sin you know so don't be over
righteous let's go to Romans 12 and we
gonna just read verse
three okay goad when you read it when
you get it Romans 12 and3 for I say
through the grace given unto me to every
man that is among you not to think of
himself more highly than he ought to
think but to think soberly according as
God has dealt to every man The Measure
of
Faith yeah so to think of ourselves more
highly than we ought to is allowing
Pride to come in and as it says in
Proverbs 6
and6 is six things that the Lord
hate and seven is an Abomination and one
of those things is pride don't be over
righteous and don't be over Wicked
that's all I
got yes sir thank you for that brother
as we move on to our next question next
question mark Ash says are there any
examples of modernday
ceremonial weddings where a pastor or
official needs to marry a couple
all right guest
caller yes there was
ceremonies and uh
uh and these ceremonies were practiced
from generation to generation even Jesus
showed up at a marriage
ceremony let's go and look at it let's
go into uh uh John second
chapter we're going to read 1 2 3 there
we going to
skip okay John 2: 1-3 say and the third
day there was a marriage in canaa of
Galilee and the mother of Jesus was
there and both Jesus was called and his
disciples to the marriage and when they
wanted wine the mother of Jesus said
unto him they have no
wine so now Jesus and his disciples was
invited to a wedding which was a ceremon
morning and when they went there Jesus
mother said look they ain't got no wine
so let's see what happens skip down and
read verses
7-9 okay verse seven says Jesus said
unto them fill the water pots with water
and they filled them up to the brim and
he sath unto them draw out now and bear
unto the governor of the feast and they
bear it when the ruler of the feast had
tasted the water that was made wine and
knew not whence it was was but the
servants which drew the water knew the
governor of the feast called the
bridegroom now so not only did he showed
up did he show up at a wedding he made
wine for the weding for the
ceremony in
fact read verse 11 verse 11 says the
beginning of miracles did Jesus in canaa
of Galilee and manifested forth his
glory and his disciples believed on him
so the first miracle that Jesus Jesus
made was at a wedding ceremony and you
had to have some official there or they
talking the governor of of the feast
some official there had to perform the
service yep that's
all all right so hope that answers your
question as we move on to our next one
all right next one little mama Hayes
says can you explain Proverbs 8 8 verse
22 is this talking about Jesus I'm
trying to explain to a coworker that
Jesus was from the beginning but was a
God in the godhead and not a possession
but
equal D what you say yeah let's go to
that Proverbs 8 and we gonna read verse
22 I'm there go ahead and read it
brother the Lord possessed me in the
beginning of his way for his works of
old notice it say the Lord possessed
me this is talking about wisdom back up
to verse one go ahead okay doth not
wisdom cry and understanding put forth
her
voice she standeth in the top of high
places by the way in the places of the
paths she C notice that wisdom is
described as a she this is
just speaking of wisdom as an attribute
that the Lord possessed but let's go
over to Proverbs 3 and look at it one
more time but it describ wisdom as a she
at the
beginning Proverbs 3 pick it up at
verse let's look at it verse 13 go ahead
brother okay happy is the man that
findeth wisdom and the man that GTH
understanding skip down to verse
15 she is more precious than rubies and
all the things thou cast desire are not
to be compared unto her skip down to
verse 18 she is a tree of life to them
that lay hold upon her and happy is
everyone that retaineth her go ahead 19
brother the Lord by wisdom hath founded
the Earth by understanding hath he
established theen heav it was by wisdom
that the Lord founded the Earth and by
understanding he established the
heaven so if wisdom is Jesus then who is
understanding now he possessed both of
those things now let's go over to
Philippians uh the second chapter and we
going to read one verse there because
you asked about him being
equal Philippians 2 and read verse 6
Philippians 2 and 6 read that get it
brother go ahead who being in the form
of God thought it not robbery to be
equal with God he said who being in the
form of God thought it not robbery to be
equal with God who was that read verse
five brother let this mind be in you
which was also in Christ Jesus that's
right so this this who was in the form
of God that thought it not re robbery to
be equal with God was Christ Jesus I
hope that helps that's all I
got all right thank you for that brother
as we move on to our next question next
question Malik Shakur says in Leviticus
19 Verse 18 who is your neighbor
According to some they say your neighbor
is the children of thy people based off
this
verse when it comes to the Commandments
of God everybody is your neighbor you
have to give those to
everybody so but let's go into that
Leviticus
19 Leviticus 19 and let's read that
verse one and two and let's see who was
speaking to who here go ahead and the
Lord spake unto Moses saying Speak unto
all the congregation of the children of
Israel and say unto them ye shall be
holy for I the Lord your God am Holy so
we see that this is the
Lord talking to Moses and speaking to
the children of Israel skip down read 17
and 18 It Go some law go ahead Thou
shalt not hate thy brother in thine
heart Thou shalt in any wise rebuke thy
neighbor and not suffer sin upon Him
Thou shalt not avenge nor bear any rudge
against the children of thy people but
Thou shalt love the neighbor as thyself
I am the Lord all right so Moses was
talking to the children of Israel here
but then it says but Thou shalt love thy
neighbor as thyself and who is Thy
Neighbor let's go into uh Matthew the
22nd
chapter Matthew the 22nd
chapter when you get there brother pick
it up at that verse 35 for me because
the Lord was always telling us that we
had to be good to the even the stranger
the one that U wasn't directly around
you Matthew 22 and pick it up at 35
let's see what Jesus said
here then one of them which was a lawyer
asked him a question tempting him and
saying Master which is the great
commandment in the
law Jesus said unto him Thou shalt love
the Lord thy God with all thy heart and
with all thy soul and with all thy mind
this is the first and great
commandment and the second is like unto
it Thou shalt love thy neighbor as
thyself so that covers all the brothers
and the sisters there that you are
supposed to be giv them all the
Commandments now you can have your block
in your neighborhood you live on and you
ain't supposed to still his lawn moow
like you ain't supposed to steal
nobody's lawn moow up on the North side
who's not directly around you so when
you talk about your neighbor hey you
supposed to give everybody the
Commandments that's how you show your
brother and your sister some love that's
all I
got all right we hope that answered your
question sister Deborah as we move
on moving on speed and power asks if you
have missed Feast even Passover over the
years even work on the Sabbath does this
mean you have willfully sined Hebrews 10
verse 26 is given all right go to
Hebrews 10 and 26 and they want to know
if they have missed a feast and a
Passover and didn't even come on the
Sabbath day is that willful sinning
Hebrews 10 and 26 and the guest caller
would take it from there okay for if we
sin willfully after that we have reached
the received the knowledge of the truth
there remaineth no more sacrifice for
sins but the whole thing
is if you can do something about it and
don't then you are sinning willfully all
that
simple now have you can keep your
passant over and and don't if you work
on the Sabbath day and don't have to
then you are sin and
willfully simple as that what I have to
say all right so make it your business
to be there when you can be there all
right we moving on to our next question
moving on Michael craw
says if you know a person that people
believe in trying to follow Ecclesiastes
12: 13 and 14 but doe drugs is there a
law of verse or anything in the Bible
that states he is committing
sin all right eclesiastes 12 let's go
there brother eclesiastes 12 13 and 14
and the guest caller will take it from
there because this is something we read
every week go ahead brother let us hear
the inclusion of the whole matter fear
God and keep his Commandments for this
is the whole duty of man for God shall
bring every work into judgment with
every secret thing whether it be good or
whether it be
evil so now he he says that sin because
he doing what
now he wants to know yes he wants to
know uh uh if you know a person that
people believe is trying to follow that
scripture but do do drugs is there a law
or verse or anything in the Bible that
states he is committing
sin well what is the definition of
sin transgression of transgression of
the law transgression of the law
now if he's doing drug or whatever maybe
he shouldn't do
it but if he ain't breaking the law then
you can't call it
sin it's all that
simple and I can't see a person that's
getting high and everything and not
sinning uh uh uh and uh uh keeping the
Commandments if he's keeping the
Commandments maybe somebody is uh uh uh
not paying
attention because of course according to
the scripture sin is the transgression
of the law so if you have not broken a
law then how can somebody call you a
sinner like people say smoking and
drinking is sin but that is not
scripture it tell you that sin is the
transgression of the law now let's go to
uh first John the 3 chapter and read
verse 4 okay 1 John 3 verse mean 1 John
3:4 says who so committeth sin
transgresseth also the law for sin is
the transgression of the
law and that's all you can do with
it that's all I have to say we'll leave
it right there sister Deborah time check
as we move to our next question yes the
time is
8:04 daughter of Judah asks how is the
first month for 2025 determined in order
to count 14 days later for pass over
does the Spring Equinox play a part in
the calendar and feast day
calculations brother Jerome does
it yes the Spring Equinox play a major
part in it uh but the way you can count
to get to that 14 days to observe the
Passover we have it on our calendar our
Israeli God calendar okay and so I'm
going to read this out because I want
you to get this it says the Spring
Equinox will fall on March the 20th
2025 at 400
a okay that's in
Jerusalem all right and we will wait for
the first uh new moon in Jerusalem after
the equin
and that new moon is going to fall fall
on March the 29th at 2 p.m in
Jerusalem right now the first day of the
month will
start um where we
are on March the 29th at
sundown 14 days after that will be April
the
11th at Sundown which is the time when
we are to observe the
Passover that's all I
got right some good light there brother
hope that answered that question as we
move on to our next next one she also
ask what does Mark 16 ver9 mean when it
says now when he rose early on the first
day of the week which we believe to be
Sunday all the other books make it known
that by Sunday morning he had already
risen and was
gone all right here go some more good
like brother Dre what you
say well sister I want to say that it
does not
say when he rose on the first day of the
week let's go read what it said unless
you're reading it out of of another
translation and what I found is because
I I did some research there are two or
three other translations that translate
it that way we read out of the KJV let's
look at what it says in Mark 16 and9 go
ahead brother read it when you get it
now when Jesus was risen early the first
day of the week he appeared first to
Mary Magdalene out of whom he had cast
seven Devils now what the way we got to
read this is the way it is written it
says now when Jesus was
risen Paul early the first day of the
week he appeared first to Mary
Magdalene when did he appear to her
early the first day of the
week and this is the woman that he
described that he had cast out seven
death
that's all it's saying because when you
read John 20 And1 let's go there and
read that John 20 and
one John
20 and one
says as it begin John TW John I'm sorry
John 20 And1 says the first day of the
week cometh Mary Magdalene early when it
was yet dark unto the supplica and seen
the stone taken away from the Suppa so
when you read this she came while it was
yet
dark on the first day of the week and
the stone was already rolled away from
the
septica you read in Matthew 28 it lets
you know he was not
there he and let's let's just go there
and just read that real quick Matthew 28
and 6
Matthew
286 yes sir says he is not here for He
Is Risen as he said come see the place
where the Lord lay so when she came
there the angel told her he is not here
he is risen so he had already
risen so what I would suggest is read
your
KJV that would be the blessing for you
sister do not read out of those other
transl ations they will trip you up
that's all I
got all right thank you for that brother
as we move on to our next question next
question if a wife won't sleep with her
husband what can he do and is that
grounds for
divorce yes
carer okay let's go to Matthew the 19th
Chapter
and
uh let's start at verse three we going
we going to uh uh uh read from
3 to
five okay Matthew 19: 3-5 say the
Pharisees also came unto him tempting
him and saying unto him is it lawful for
a man to put away his wife for every
cause and he answered and said unto them
them have ye not read that he which made
them at the beginning made them male and
female and said for this cause shall a
man leave father and mother and shall
cleave to his wife and the Twain and a
twain shall be one
flesh now take note they ask him should
put away his wife for every cause in
they that's mean reason for every reason
but we're going to skip all that and get
right out what Jesus said skip down to
verse
18 and uh uh not 18 I'm sorry
uh eight verse eight rather okay verse
eight says he saith unto them Moses
because of the hardness of your hearts
suffered you to put away your wives but
from the beginning it was not
so go
and I say unto you whosoever shall put
away his wife except it be for
fornication and shall marry another
committeth adultery and who so Marth her
which is put away doeth commit
adultery okay so now if you married and
she go lay with somebody else we ain't
going to call it fornication we going to
call the
marriage definition of and commit
adultery then she can put away but if
she have not laid with
nobody I'm sorry brother he
yours yours oh I
got all right hope that answers your
question brother and sister Deborah I
believe we're going to take a trip into
new
territory yes that is correct we are now
into tonight's Q&A for Wednesday
February the 12th
2025 philosop he asked in Genesis 32 and
no scriptures are given did Jacob
wrestle with an angel or was it Jesus I
have seen different takes and want to
know what the real fact is right well we
know it wasn't Jesus but let's go um
they didn't give us scripture let's go
to Genesis 32 we open this up to the
panel too Genesis
32 because this is
yeah no vers no verses were given just
Genesis 32 I think she was asking verse
24 because that's where they uh where he
wrestled with the man I mean yeah we're
gonna do a little interpretation but she
wanted to know if this was a Jesus or an
angel let's pick it up at verse one and
two and let's kind of set the tone in we
skip down at 24 go ahead brother okay uh
Genesis 32:1 says and Jacob went on his
way and the angels of God met him and
when Jacob saw them he said this is
God's host and he called the name of the
place Mah
Mahan okay so we just wanted to show
that the Angels was there but go ahead
skip down 24 and then let's open it up
to the panel go ahead and Jacob was left
alone and there Wrestled a man with him
until the breaking of the day
okay let's go directly and this go to
Hosea the 12th chapter read verses 2
through 4 okay Hosea 12
yeah that was Hosea
12 2 through 4 okay Hosea 12 2-4
says the Lord ha also a controversy with
Judah and will punish Jacob according to
his ways according to his doings will he
recompense him he took his brother by
the heel in the womb and by his strength
he had power with God yay he had Pro he
had power over the angel and prevailed
he wept and made supplication unto him
he found him in bethl and there he spake
with
us now he said now now what verse did
you just read that was verse four
sir what it say the beginning of the
four verse yay he had power over the
angel and
Prevail uhhuh and he
prevailed okay that's why he say you
have power with as a prince with man and
God so there was an angel that he
wrestled with that's where he had the
power because when the angel said let me
go he said I will not un let until you
bless me that's when he said what's your
name my name is Jacob he said should no
longer be called Jacob but Israel so he
had power over the angel other words he
wrestled Angel and he
prevailed okay yep that is straight to
the point and we hope that answers your
question all right we're going to move
on to our next one next one one one says
I work in architecture and engineering
Fields sometimes these companies design
Sunday churches or other Pagan religious
buildings should I refuse to work on the
design for these projects if
assigned oh you there just to do your
job you there to do a job you there to
keep a roof over your head and food on
the table and that would apply for any
electrician plumber anybody else that
may be a part of that building but for
you to say you don't want to work on it
just because it's a pagan
building that doesn't apply to you you
just do your job and that's all I
got all right we leave it go ahead guess
call Soldier ask Jesus what should he do
maybe somebody can dig it up right quick
and he answered him and told him
yeah we in search mode for
that we are in search mode for
that um let's see
here uh Mark 12 and 17 let's see if that
might be what you're talking about I
think L 3 and
14 Luke 3 and 14 okay I'm there Luke 3
and4 Let's
see and the soul and I'm sorry Luke 3
and14 says and the soldiers likewise
demanded of him saying and what shall we
do and he said unto them do violence to
no man neither accuse any falsely and be
content with your
wages in short he didn't say stop being
a soldier didn't he
he just said don't you know don't be uh
don't don't uh you know don't take no
bribes in other words don't be violent
with nobody that you don't have to be
violent with cuz soldiers are necessary
so just like he told that soldiers just
do your job then that's what you do you
do your
job all right thank you for that hit
there Sean as we move on to our next
question next question Malik Shakura
asks where can I find where David said
the spirit of God spoke by him
concerning Jesus and he also wants to
know was Moses speaking to Jesus in
Exodus
33:20 if so was no one able to see the
face of Jesus at that time
also GRE what you got let's go to
uh where can I find
David said the spirit of God spake by
him let's go to second Samuel the 23rd
chapter 2 Samuel the 23rd chapter okay
I'm there we gonna pick it up at verse
one now now these be the last words of
David David the son of Jesse said and
the man who was raised up on high the
anointed of the god of Jacob and the
sweet son psalmist of Israel said the
spirit of the Lord spake by me and his
word was in my tongue yes sir that's
where it said read verse three brother
the god of Israel said the rock of
Israel spake to me he that ruleth over
men must be just ruling in the fear of
God and First Corinthians will tell you
that rock was Christ in 1 Corinthians 10
1-4 but the spirit of the Lord spoke by
David in many of the
Psalms spoke by
David uh the second part of that
question was was what sister Deborah was
Moses speaking to Jesus in Exodus 33
verse 20 if so was no one able to see
the face of Jesus at that time also
let's go to Exodus 33 and we going to uh
let's let's see Exodus
33 and pick it up at uh verse 9 okay and
we'll read into it Exodus 33 and9 go
ahead and it came to pass as Moses
entered into the Tabernacle the Cloudy
pillar descended and stood at the door
of the Tabernacle and the Lord talked
with Moses so the Lord came down in a
cloudy pillar and talk to Moses go ahead
and all the people saw the Cloudy pillar
stand at the Tabernacle door and all the
people rose up and worship every man in
his tent
door and the Lord spake unto Moses face
to face as a man speaketh unto his
friend and he turned again into the camp
but his servant Joshua the son of nun a
young man departed not out of the
Tabernacle so it say the Lord spake onto
Moses face to face but Moses did not see
his face he spake onto him skip down to
verse ver skip down to verse uh 20 now
go ahead and he said thou cast not see
my face and there shall no man see me
and
live so so in verse 17
Moses ask that can he see the Lord's
Glory read Verse 18 go ahead and he said
I beseech thee show me thy Glory
so go down to verse 22 and by 21 and see
what the Lord did go ahead and the Lord
said behold there is a place by me and
thou shalt stand upon a
rock and it shall come to pass while my
glory passes by that that I will put
thee in a cliff of The Rock and will
cover thee with my hand while I pass
by and I will take away my hand and thou
shalt see my back Parts but my face
shall not be seen so they he didn't see
the Lord's face he saw his glory and the
Lord covered him and let him see his
back part but then in the other place
where it say he saw him face to face he
came down in a cloud and that's what
they dealt with so I hope that that
helps if anybody want to add something
yeah there's another part of this
question he said also was Moses speaking
to Jesus in
Exodus going to St John 5 and read verse
37 let and let us said L that is right
that's right
St John 5 and 37
says and the father himself which has
seen has sent me ha borne witness of me
ye have neither heard his voice at any
time nor seen his
shape so if you ain't never heard the
voice of the father seen his shape at
any time that let you know then he was
dealing with Jesus okay that is right
that's right brother thank you for that
guest call
all right hope that answered your
question there thank you for that addon
let us move on to our next
question next one most love asked did
Jesus get baptized in his father's name
Jesus because I don't remember John
calling a name when he baptized Jesus
yes call
him acts 19th Chapter and read verse
4 okay Acts 19
and verse 4
says 19 and 4
[Music]
says then said Paul John verily baptized
with the baptism of repentance saying
unto the people that they Shall Believe
on him which shall come after him that
is on Christ
Jesus John didn't baptize him in the
name of the father he baptized him unto
repentance
okay all right hope that answered your
question next question next question be
alert as can family members who do not
keep God's Commandments Follow You Into
the Wilderness you don't keep the
Commandments can you go into the
Wilderness guess
caller of course you can but once you
get there let me show you what you have
to do let's go into Ezekiel the 20th
chapter and read verses 3 3-
38 okay Ezekiel 20:
33-38 says as I live sayeth the Lord God
surely with a mighty hand and with a
stretched out arm and with Fury poured
out will I rule over you and I will
bring you out I will bring you out from
the people and will gather you out of
the countries where in ye are scattered
with a mighty hand and with a stretched
out arm when with Fury poured out
and I will bring you into the Wilderness
of the people and there will I plead
with you face to face like as I pleaded
with your fathers in the wilderness of
the land of Egypt so will I plead with
you sayeth the Lord God and I will cause
you and I will cause you to pass under
the rod and I will bring you into the
bond of the Covenant and I will Purge
out from among you the rebels with them
that transgress against me and I will
bring them forth out of the country
where they sourn and they shall not
enter into the land of Israel and ye
shall know that I am the
Lord going cause you to pass under the
rod and bring you into the bond of the
Covenant so if you want to in the
Covenant is is what God made with
Abraham because he's the only one he
really made a covenant with so let me
show you how you're brought into the
bond of the Covenant let's go into
Galatians the 3 chapter
and we going to uh
uh we going to read the uh starting from
uh verse
26 to
29 okay that is Galatians 3: 26- 29
which says for ye are all the children
of God by faith in Christ Jesus for as
many of you as have been baptized into
Christ have put on Christ there is
neither Jew nor Greek there is neither
Bond nor free there is neither male nor
female for ye are all one in Christ
Jesus and if ye be Christ then are ye
Abraham's seed and HS according to the
promise oh now that according to the
promise because God made the Covenant
with Abraham so now if you go into
Wilderness you you're not baptized then
you going to have to be brought into the
bond of the Covenant that mean you going
to be
baptized yeah and once you
baptized then you are Abraham and uh and
you're going to be baptized in the name
of Jesus then are you Abraham's seed and
a according to the Covenant of the
promise so sure it don't matter whether
they baptized or not when they go into
the Wilderness it matter whether they
get baptized once they get in there
because if they refuse to get baptized
then that's being a being rebellious and
the Lord say he going to cut off uh uh
uh the rebels and you ain't going to get
into the land because he going to kill
you right there in the
wilderness yep all right don't be a
rebel hope that answers your question as
we move on to our next next one Jennifer
Love ask does God speak to us like he
did with Moses or is it just through his
word via the Bible brother
Julius the Lord speak to us through his
word and he talked to uh
Moses face to face like Dre said let's
go to St John the 14th chapter let's
look at how the Lord speak to her speak
to us
today St John the 14th chapter brother
James we read vers four uh uh 15 to 18
and Skip okay first John 14 15 says if
ye love me keep my Commandments yes and
I will pray the father and he shall give
you another comforter that he may abide
with you forever yes even the spirit of
Truth whom the world have who the world
cannot receive because it seeth him not
neither knoweth him but ye know him for
he dwelleth with you and shall be in you
so you got to have that word that the
Lord said his angel and bring that word
to you that which is already written uh
Verse 18 I will not leave you
comfortless I will come to you how is it
gonna come to us sisters and brothers
verse
23 Jesus answered and said unto you if a
man love me he will keep my words he
keep my what my words you got to read
his word his Bible which is the mind of
God Genesis the revelation if a man love
me he will keep my words go ahead and my
father will love him and we will come
unto him and make our Abode with him
verse 26 and I'm done but the comforter
which is the Holy Ghost whom the father
will send in my name he shall teach you
all things and bring all things to your
remembrance whatsoever I have said unto
you so that mean you got to read his
book and then you like the books said
you eat the book get the wisdom
knowledge and understanding live by them
Commandments because that's what you
going to be governed by so now how do
the Lord come to you today thou shall
not kill thou shall not steal it's in
the word you walk in that word because
it is written and you live in it so
that's how he talks to you through his
word that's all I got I like I like to
back up I like to back up to the last
question person text me and said well
the people was talking about the woman
that fled Into the Wilderness in the
12th chapter of
Revelation okay deal and all deal and
all there ain't nothing that said you
have to be baptized to be a part of the
woman that fled Into the Wilderness but
you going to have to be baptized to get
into God's kingdom and get into the uh
get into the land of
Israel that mean if you're not baptized
you're not under the Covenant that mean
the only thing I can say for sure is
that you will not be in the first
resurrection yeah so when the Lord come
back he going to come to them same
wildness where the people are then you
going to have to be brought into the
bond of the covant either way you look
at it all I have to say all right sister
Deborah time check because time is a
ticket yes uh the time is
8:32 and again with Jennifer Love uh
question
uh you get the word you uh God speaks to
you through his word via the Bible
that's the way you get the word
so on to the next question Kaitlyn Gable
asks for you to
explain Deuteronomy 12: 15 and 22 she
says I'm a little confused where it says
the unclean and the clean eat
thereof all right that's a popular
question that pops up from time to time
Dre what you say let's go and read that
uh Deuteronomy 12 we're going to read
verse
15 and then we'll read verse uh 22 go
ahead get it brother notwithstanding
thou mayest kill and eat flesh in all
thy Gates whatsoever thy Soul lusteth
after Accord to the blessing of the Lord
thy God which which he has given Thee
the unclean and the clean may eat there
of as of the Rob book and as of the
heart so this is talking about the
people that are clean are unclean we'll
eat thereof but we'll we'll prove this
out read verse 22 go ahead even as the
robug and the heart is eaten so Thou
shalt eat them and eat them the unclean
and the clean shall eat of them alike
that's right again this is talking about
the people but let's go to Deuteronomy
15 and we G to read verse 22 there
Deuteronomy 15 and verse
22 Thou shalt eat it within thy Gates
the unclean and the clean person shall
eat it alike as the robug and as the
heart you see right there it says the
unclean
and clean person shall eat it alike as
the Rob up and as the hard so this is
talking about whether you clean or
unclean you will eat thereof that's all
I yes sir brother Dre the dietary law
hey written with a pen of iron yes sir
brother all right brother thank you for
that as we move on to our next
question next question a Thomas asked
who is one from the North in Isaiah 41
verse
25 one from the north Isaiah 41 and 25
let's go there James I'm there I guess C
would take it from
there Isaiah 41 and 25 says I have
raised up one from the north and he
shall come from the rising of the sun
shall he call upon my name and he shall
come upon princes as upon mortar and as
the Potter treadeth
clay now this is talking about Jesus
yeah I we back
up I we back up to verse four verse two
rather read two and four okay this is
the same one you can say come from the
North and then from the rising of the
sun that's North and there is Northwest
but then we going to show you this is
talking about Jesus can't be a
man okay verse two four read it okay who
raised up oh I'm sorry Isaiah 41: 2-4
says who raised up the righteous man
from the East called him to his foot
gave the Nations before him and made him
rule over Kings he gave them as the dust
of as the dust to his sword and is
driven stubble to his Bo he pursued them
and P and passed safely even by the way
that he had not gone with his feet who
had wrought oh now this is the guy the
same one you know that was sent to do
this and who and read verse four who who
this say this is verse four who ha
wrought and done it calling the
generations from the beginning I the
Lord the first and and with the last I
am
he so he said I am he so he is the one
that was sent to deal with these people
now let's read uh verse 25 one more time
okay I have raised up one from the north
and Sh and he shall come from the rising
of the sun shall he call upon my name
and he shall come upon princes as upon
mortar and as the Potter treadeth clay
now let's go and look at this guy let's
go into uh
Psalms chapter
2 and we're going to read from 2 to 12
we're going to read quick okay
okay Psalms
[Music]
two and verse 2 to2 says the kings of
the earth set themselves and the rulers
take counsel together against the Lord
and against his anointing saying let us
break their bands aunder and Cast Away
their cords from us he that sth in the
heavens shall laugh the Lord shall have
them in derision then shall he speak
upon them in his wrath and Vex them in
his sore displeasure yet have I set my
kingdom upon my Holy Hill of Zion I will
declare the decree the Lord has said
unto me thou art my son this day have I
begotten thee ask of me the Lord is the
one that set him on high and this is
when he and this is when he come back he
say so now so he speaking himself said I
will declare decree the Lord and said
unto me thou my son this day have I
begotten thee continue to read ask of me
and I shall give Thee the Heathen of for
thine inheritance and the uttermost
parts
of then in Isaiah then the Lord say he
gave them people that you
know to the sword
going give to Heathen the nation as an
inheritance what's he going to do to
them go ahead and the uttermost and the
uttermost parts of the Earth for thy
possession Thou shalt break them with a
rod of iron Thou shalt Dash them in
pieces like a Potter's
vessel like his
[Music]
vessel goad be wise now therefore oh ye
Kings be instructed ye judges of the
Earth serve the Lord with fear and
rejoice with trembling kiss the son
least he be angry and ye perish from the
way when his wrath is kindled but a
little blessed are all they that put
their trust in
him so we going to break them in pieces
and treat him like like Potter dressel
and he going to Ru with a rod of ir this
is the son so to make sure we understand
who this is let's go the last place
Revelation the 12th chapter read verses
one and two and Skip down to
five Revelation 12 vers is revelation 12
veres 1- 2 says and there appeared a
great woman in heaven a woman clothed
with the sun and the moon under her feet
and upon her head a crown of 12 stars
and she being with now Genesis the 7
chap 37 chapter will let you know this
that is talking about the woman is
Israel
Okay so she had and let's see who this
son is she was travailing in birth to do
what and she being with child cried
travailing in birth and pain to be
delivered verse five
says verse five says and she brought
forth a Manchild who was to rule all
nations with a rod of iron and her child
was caught up unto God and his
throne so that guy in Isaiah
41 and uh uh uh 25 is talking about
Jesus all I have to say all right hope
that answered your question as we move
on to our next
one uh next question Elizabeth cochrell
says I'm reading but is there any
Scripture in the Old Testament that
speaks of Jesus Christ's Kingdom to come
and that Zion is not in heaven all right
Zion is not in heaven brother
Jerome yes we got scripture on that um
let's deal with the Jesus Kingdom first
let's go to Daniels chapter
7 and read verse 13 and 14 then we're
going to skip okay Daniel 7: 13 says and
I saw in the night vision and behold
behold one like the son of man came with
the clouds of heaven and came to the
Ancient of Days and they brought him
near before him and there was given him
dominion and glory and a kingdom that
all people na Nations and languages
should serve him his Dominion is an
everlasting Dominion which shall not
pass away and his kingdom that which
shall not be destroyed skip down to
verse 27 okay and the kingdom and
dominion and the greatness of the
Kingdom Under the whole Heaven shall be
given to the people of the Saints of the
most high whose kingdom is an
everlasting Kingdom and all Dominion
Shall Serve and Obey him yeah and if you
go to Psalms let's go to Psalms
132 because um the
Zion that he talking about is the same
thing you reading about here is on this
Earth okay so let's let's deal with that
Zion okay Psalms 132 verse 13-
14 for the Lord had chosen Zion he had
desired it for his habitation this is my
rest forever here will I dwell for I
have desired it as he dwelling in heaven
right now sitting on the father's throne
but when he return he going to dwell on
this Zion and this going to be his
habitation forever so when he return He
dwelling in this
Zion
forever okay and that's on this earth
right there in Jerusalem Zion is just
another name for
jerus that's all I
got all right thank you thank you for
that as we move on to our next question
next question
zando football wants explanation on job
23:
1-6 what did job mean by what he was
saying all right job was saying a lot of
things there but he was in great
Agony and he wanted to know from the
Lord why he was going through what he
was going through because he went from
very blessed to sitting in the ashes
full of Swords but let's go and read
that joob 23
just keep in mind like I say he was in
great Agony and pain right here go
ahead then job answered and said even
today is my complaint bitter my stroke
is heavier than my groaning oh that I
knew where I might find him that I might
come even to his seat I will order my
cause before him and fill my mouth with
arguments I would know the words which
he would answer me and understand what
he would say un me will he plead against
me with his great power no but he would
put strength in me job was saying even
in at verse four I would order my cause
before him and fill my mouth with
arguments with God W to know why he was
in that situation he was in so that's
what Joe's position was at that time but
if you go at Job 42 let's turn over
there right quick job 42 two I'm there
and pick it up um at that verse
one then job answered the Lord and
said I know that thou cast do everything
and that no thought can be withholden
from
thee who is he that hideth counsel
without knowledge therefore have I
uttered that I understood not things too
wonderful for me which I knew not yes
and so he was you can read more more of
that and he'll let you know that he
humbled himself before God and was like
Hey you know all of that talking about
arguing with you and things of that
nature hey he came to sense and say God
is too wonderful and know all things
that's all I
got all right hope that answered your
question as we move on as time is a
ticking because we are truly having fun
sister Deborah yes uh Story Time says
Jesus said in Romans 2 verse1 for there
is no respect of persons with God but
turn around and say in Romans 9 verse1
15 God will have mercy on whom he'll
have mercy on is this a
contradiction this question stems from
why the thief seemed to be favored even
though he was on the cross for he is
wrong doing brother
Jerome no that's not a contradiction um
the issue is really uh repentance that's
the that's the real issue because you
got those that uh they doing right they
doing what the Lord say then they change
their mind in
turn then you got the flip side to that
you got those that's been doing wrong
doing wrong and then all of a sudden
they consider and they change and and
they do
right all right and the Lord he said
he'll he'll show Mercy unto those that
turn and and repent okay so when you
talk about the thief on the cross that's
exactly what he did and the Lord knoweth
our heart he tried to Reigns he know
exactly if you sincere when you repented
or when you wasn't sincere when you
repented cuz he lookth on the heart okay
so he not a respector of person's in
judgment okay so now let's look let's
look at
um Proverbs 24 and
23 and then we going to go to Exodus
34 see he we goingon to read The Exodus
34 he say he he show Mercy but he shall
in no wise clear the guilty so and I
have you
happen to be Wicked at the time you turn
and change the Lord will have mercy
because he going to look in your heart
and see that it's sincere and he gonna
forgive you okay but read that Proverbs
24 and
23 okay these things also belong to the
wise it is not good to have respect of
persons in judgment yeah so the Lord
don't have respect of persons in
judgment either okay and read that
Exodus 346 and 7 34 Exodus 34 6 and 7
says and the Lord passed by before him
and proclaimed the Lord and proclaimed
the Lord the Lord God merciful and
gracious longsuffering and abundant in
goodness and Truth keeping Mercy for
thousands forgiving iniquity and trans
thank you for that hope that answered
that question our next one next one
manessa dop ask during the Millennium
period with those born in that period
still see
death let's go to um Isaiah
65 18 through
20 because even during that time no man
would still live to be a thousand years
old so let's read that this is when the
Lord's going to
restore long life back into the program
but it won't be past A Thousand Years
Isaiah 65 read 18 through 20 go ahead
brother but be ye glad and rejoice
forever in that which I create for
behold I create Jerusalem a rejoicing
and our people a joy and I will rejoice
in Jerusalem and joy in my people and
the voice of weeping shall be no more
heard in her nor the voice of crying
there shall there shall be no more then
an infant of days nor an old man that ha
not filled his days for the child shall
die 100 years old but the sinner being
100 years old shall be a cursed Lord go
give you a while to get it together and
uh if you don't then hey you going bring
a curse on yourself but yeah it still be
flesh and blood so there still be death
going on at that time that's all I
got hope that answers your question
sister debah we coming down to the
wre yes Renee Israel as in Leviticus 23:
27 on the 10th day of the seven month is
the day of atonement but verse 32 says
the ninth day of that same month
celebrate your Sabbath do we have a
Sabbath
Julius yes yes let's go to Leviticus 23
James and 27 I'm there
cuz you you still got to keep this we're
going to show you why when you get it go
ahead brother also on the 10th day of
the SE of the seventh month there shall
be a day of atonement it shall be in
holy convocation unto you and ye shall
afflict your souls and offer an offering
made by fire unto the Lord so now let's
go to verse
32 it shall be it shall be unto you a
Sabbath of rest and ye shall afflict
your souls and and the ninth day of the
month at even from even unto even shall
ye celebrate your Sabbath so now the
answer is the ninth day of the seventh
month at evening becomes the 10th
day because he told you in Genesis that
the evening and the morning that's why
it says at evening that means sun down
in darkness that's when on the ninth day
becomes the 10th day and it and on that
we keep the day of
atonement y that's that's all I
got all right we hope you understood
that as we move on to our next
question next question and C ask Will
flesh and blood still have to work
during Jesus Christ 1,00 year
reign J
room H
absolutely man don't work you ain't
gonna eat that's
right yeah let's go to that uh Isaiah 65
and we gonna read 17 through 23 even
during the um Kingdom Thousand-Year
Kingdom you know you still gonna have to
work six
days right do all your work and then on
the seventh day you gonna rest that's
going to be going on throughout that
thousand years yeah okay so but let's
read that Isaiah 65 verse
17-23 for behold I create a new he
create new heavens and a new Earth and
the former shall not be remembered nor
come into mine but be ye glad and
rejoice forever in that which I create
for behold I create Jerusalem a
rejoicing and her people of joy and I
will rejoice in Jerusalem and joy in my
people and the voice of weeping shall be
no more heard in heard nor the voice of
crying there shall be no more then an
infant of days nor an old man that ha
not filled his days for the child shall
die a hundred years old but the sinner
be hundred years old shall be a cursed
yeah so that's doing the that's doing
the son's Kingdom that's not happening
in the father's Kingdom okay now keep
reading because we still got to work and
they shall build houses and inhabit them
and they shall plant Vineyards and eat
the fruit of them they shall not build
and and another inhabit they shall not
plant and another eat for as the days of
a tree are the days of my people and
mine elect shall long enjoy the work of
their hands they shall not labor in vain
nor bring forth for trouble for they are
the seed of the bless of the Lord and
their offspring with them yeah and this
is the Flesh and Blood that's all I got
all right see well will be working
during that time yeah all right thank
you for that brother next question next
question Zion says I know when the pope
moves into the temple it is time to flee
do we go straight to an airport if so do
we ask for a ticket to a country in the
East I'm confused I don't want to miss
my ride we don't want you to miss your
ride either guess
caller well this is one we have to wait
on just like Israel didn't even know how
they were going to get out of the land
of Egypt they
never mind that God would spit a sea and
take them across
dry yep so find out when that time come
but the only thing I can do is confirm
the method of your traveling let's go
into Isaiah 60 and read Verses 4 and
Skip down and read verse 8 and
N okay Isaiah
60:4 says lift up thine eyes round about
and see all they all they gather
themselves together they come to thee
thy son shall come from far and thy
daughter shall be nursed at thy
side verse 8 and9 says who are these
that fly as a cloud and as the doves to
their Windows surely the ow th sht wait
for me and the ships of tarus first to
bring thy sons from Far their silver and
their gold with them unto the name of
the Lord thy God and to the Holy One of
Israel because he hath glorified
thee they let you know you going to go
back by ship and
plains but uh you have to wait until the
time come the Lord will show you what to
do don't uh be scared all you have to do
is be right and have the
so let see all right hope that answered
your question sister de we are down to
our last question or two next one all
right just know as in Matthew and it's
and no verses are given Jesus as spanned
on the law but condemns the Pharisees
for doing the same did Jesus make the
law void when he changed it absolutely
not brother Dre what you say no Jesus
did not make void the law and uh the
book tell you in Isaiah 42 that he
magnified the
law and made it to make it
honorable and that's exactly what he did
but let's go to Matthew 5 and read verse
17 okay Matthew
5:17 says think not that I come to
destroy the law or the prophets I am not
come to destroy but to fulfill a lot of
people read that to say that he
fulfilled the law but he fulfilled what
was written of him to come and
do let's go read what he fulfilled let's
go to Luke 24 and read verse 44-
46 Luke 24 yes Luke 24 44- 46 when you
get
46 okay it says and he said unto them
these are the words which I speak unto
you while I was yet with you that all
things must be fulfilled which were
written in the law of Moses and in the
prophets and in the Psalms concerning me
then that's what he fulfilled the all
the things that was written of him that
he was to do when he came to be the
sacrifice for our sins but there is more
to fulfill
he did not destroy the law now in terms
of him changing it he magnified it so if
you continue to read in Matthew 5 he
lets you know you have heard this but
that now as it pertains to the Pharisees
let's go to Mark 7 and read verses
5-9 because they not dealing with the
law here Mark 7 5-9 go ahead brother
then the Pharisees and scribes asked him
why walk not the dis thy disciples
according to the tradition of el of the
elders but eat bread with unwashed hands
now notice he said you eating bread with
unwashed hands and you not walking after
the
tradition of the elders go ahead brother
and he answered and said unto them well
hath Isaias prophesied of you Hypocrites
as it is written this people honth me
with their lips but their heart is far
from me how be it in vain they do
worship me teaching for doctrines the
Commandments of men and that is the
difference that's the
difference Jesus magnified the law they
gave you the tradition of the elders
huge
difference I hope that helped yes sir
indeed it did sister Deborah time chck
the time is
9:01 oh we have ran out of time we want
to thank everybody from all around the
world who joined us if you submitted a
question and we didn't get to it please
don't resubmit it sister devil would
take it and put it into rotation we also
want to send out a reminder that we are
in our black history series this
Saturday at 520 West 38th Street in
Riverdale Chicago Illinois
60827 we will be doing doing our next
lesson which is spiritual death and
Resurrection please feel free to join us
so you can learn of the black history
and also until we all come together
again be safe be blessed stay prayerful
and may the Lord have mercy on us all as
our brother James closes us
out Our Father which art in heaven
Hallowed be thy name thy kingdom come
thy will be done
in Earth as it is in heaven give us this
day our daily bread and forgive us our
debts as we forgive our Deb TOs and lead
us not into temptation but Deliver Us
from Evil for thine is the kingdom and
the power and the glory forever in Jesus
name we pray